ILGWU Oral History 5780 OH
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILGWU Oral History
1973-1986
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union
5780 OH
93.44 cubic feet
12.9 linear ft.
Oral histories (document genres).
This collection contains recordings of oral history interviews with officers, staff, and members of the ILGWU.
6268727
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, January 24, 2013
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, April 02, 2019
Biographical / Historical
The International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union was once one of the largest labor unions in the United States founded in 1900 by local union delegates representing about 2,000 members in cities in the northeastern United States. It was one of the first U.S. Unions to have a membership consisting of mostly females, and it played a key role in the labor history of the 1920s and 1930s. The union is generally referred to as the "ILGWU" or the "ILG". The ILGWU grew in geographical scope, membership size, and political influence to become one of the most powerful forces in American organized labor by mid-century. Representing workers in the women's garment industry, the ILGWU worked to improve working and living conditions of its members through collective bargaining agreements, training programs, health care facilities, cooperative housing, educational opportunities, and other efforts. The ILGWU merged with the Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union in 1995 to form the Union of Needle trades, Industrial and Textile Employees (UNITE). UNITE merged with the Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees Union (HERE) in 2004 to create a new union known as UNITE HERE. The two unions that formed UNITE in 1995 represented only 250,000 workers between them, down from the ILGWU's peak membership of 450,000 in 1969.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5780: ILGWU records 5780/110 OHT: ILGWU. Oral Histories 5780/111: ILGWU Archives Department Records
Clothing workers -- Labor unions -- History -- United States; Clothing workers -- United States -- History; Clothing industry -- United States -- History; Appleton, Shelley; Bachrach, Michael; Borenstein, Sarah; Breslow, Israel; Conticelli, Antony; Denaro, John; Diamond, Moe; Dubinsky, David, 1892-1982; Faier, Jack; Fedorin, Rose Kaufman; Follman, Benjamin; Gatti, Frank; Gingold, David; Goldstein, Eugene; Graeber, Ruth Rubinstein; Gross, Murray; Larsen, Clara; Laxner, Bertha Mandel; Minkoff, Nathaniel; Newman, Pauline; Novik, Morris S., 1903-; Parenti, Enrico; Pepe, Pauline; Plotkin, Abraham, 1893-1988; Read, Lula; Rosenberg, Rose Newmark; Ross, William; Sandhaus, Samuel; Schindler, Harry; Schlesinger, Emil; Shane, Bernard; Shrog, Nettie Harary; Shuster, Mary Goff; Silverman, Jennie; Stean, Josephine; Stulberg, Louis, 1901-1977; Teper, Lazare, 1908-; Tyler, Gus; Weiss, Ida; Weiss, Ida; Zelinka, David; Zimmerman, Charles S., 1896-1983
6268727
- Reel-to-reel tape recordings of oral history interviews (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  Includes David Dubinsky, David Gingold, Antony Conticelli, and Emil Schlesinger
- Reel-to-reel tape recordings of oral history interviews (Box 2, Folder 1)
  Includes Emil Schlesinger, Harry Schindler, and David Zelinka
- David Dubinsky (Box 3)
  - David Dubinsky, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    O.H. 2
- David Dubinsky (Box 4)
  - David Dubinsky, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- David Dubinsky (Box 5)
  - David Dubinsky, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- David Dubinsky (Box 6)
  - David Dubinsky, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- David Gingold by Gus Tyler (Box 7)
  - David Gingold, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    O.H. 3
- David Gingold by Gus Tyler (Box 8)
  - David Gingold, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- David Gingold by Gus Tyler (Box 9)
  - David Gingold, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- David Gingold by Gus Tyler (Box 10)
  - David Gingold, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- David Gingold by Gus Tyler (Box 11)
  - David Gingold, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- David Gingold by Gus Tyler (Box 12)
  - David Gingold, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- David Gingold by Gus Tyler (Box 13)
  - David Gingold, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Copies of oral history interviews (Box 14, Folder 1)
- David Gingold by Gus Tyler (Box 14CD)
  - David Gingold, 1974 (Box 14CD, Folder 1)
- Copies of oral history interviews (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Emil Schlesinger (Box 15CD)
  - Emil Schlesinger, 1974 (Box 15CD, Folder 1)
    O.H. 5
- Emil Schlesinger (Box 16)
  - Emil Schlesinger, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Emil Schlesinger (Box 17)
  - Emil Schlesinger, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Emil Schlesinger (Box 18)
  - Emil Schlesinger, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Emil Schlesinger (Box 19)
  - Emil Schlesinger, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Emil Schlesinger (Box 20)
  - Emil Schlesinger, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Emil Schlesinger (Box 21)
  - Emil Schlesinger, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Emil Schlesinger (Box 22)
  - Emil Schlesinger, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Emil Schlesinger (Box 23)
  - Emil Schlesinger, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Emil Schlesinger (Box 24)
  - Emil Schlesinger, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- David Zelinka (Box 25)
  - David Zelinka, 1975 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    O.H. 6
- David Zelinka (Box 26)
  - David Zelinka, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 1)
- David Zelinka (Box 27)
  - David Zelinka, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 1)
- Antony Conticelli (Box 28)
  - Antony Conticelli, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    O.H. 7
- Antony Conticelli (Box 29)
  - Antony Conticelli, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 1)
- Antony Conticelli (Box 30)
  - Antony Conticelli, 1975 (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Antony Conticelli (Box 31)
  - Antony Conticelli, 1975 (Box 31, Folder 1)
- Antony Conticelli (Box 32)
  - Antony Conticelli, 1975 (Box 32, Folder 1)
- Antony Conticelli (Box 33)
  - Antony Conticelli, 1975 (Box 33, Folder 1)
- Antony Conticelli (Box 34)
  - Antony Conticelli, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 1)
- Antony Conticelli (Box 35)
  - Antony Conticelli, 1975 (Box 35, Folder 1)
- William Ross (Box 36)
  - William Ross, 1975 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    O.H. 10
- William Ross (Box 37)
  - William Ross, 1975 (Box 37, Folder 1)
- William Ross (Box 38)
  - William Ross, 1975 (Box 38, Folder 1)
- William Ross (Box 39)
  - William Ross, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 1)
- William Ross (Box 40)
  - William Ross, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 1)
- William Ross (Box 41)
  - William Ross, 1975 (Box 41, Folder 1)
- Samuel Sandhaus (Box 42)
  - Samuel Sandhaus, 1975 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    O.H. 11
- Samuel Sandhaus (Box 43)
  - Samuel Sandhaus, 1975 (Box 43, Folder 1)
- Samuel Sandhaus (Box 44)
  - Samuel Sandhaus, 1975 (Box 44, Folder 1)
- Louis Stulberg (Box 45)
  - Louis Stulberg, 1976 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    O.H. 12
- Louis Stulberg (Box 46)
  - Louis Stulberg, 1976 (Box 46, Folder 1)
- Louis Stulberg (Box 47)
  - Louis Stulberg, 1976 (Box 47, Folder 1)
- Louis Stulberg (Box 48)
  - Louis Stulberg, 1976 (Box 48, Folder 1)
- Louis Stulberg (Box 49)
  - Louis Stulberg, 1976 (Box 49, Folder 1)
- Louis Stulberg (Box 50)
  - Louis Stulberg, 1976 (Box 50, Folder 1)
- Louis Stulberg (Box 51)
  - Louis Stulberg, 1976 (Box 51, Folder 1)
- Louis Stulberg (Box 52)
  - Louis Stulberg, 1976 (Box 52, Folder 1)
- Louis Stulberg (Box 53)
  - Louis Stulberg, 1976 (Box 53, Folder 1)
- Louis Stulberg (Box 54)
  - Louis Stulberg, 1976 (Box 54, Folder 1)
- Louis Stulberg (Box 55)
  - Louis Stulberg, 1976 (Box 55, Folder 1)
- Louis Stulberg (Box 56)
  - Louis Stulberg, 1976 (Box 56, Folder 1)
- Louis Stulberg (Box 57)
  - Louis Stulberg, 1976 (Box 57, Folder 1)
- Louis Stulberg (Box 58)
  - Louis Stulberg, 1976 (Box 58, Folder 1)
- Bernard Shane (Box 59)
  - Bernard Shane (Box 59, Folder 1)
    O.H. 13
- Bernard Shane (Box 60)
  - Bernard Shane (Box 60, Folder 1)
- Bernard Shane (Box 61)
  - Bernard Shane (Box 61, Folder 1)
- Bernard Shane (Box 62)
  - Bernard Shane (Box 62, Folder 1)
- Bernard Shane (Box 63)
  - Bernard Shane (Box 63, Folder 1)
- Bernard Shane (Box 64)
  - Bernard Shane (Box 64, Folder 1)
- Bernard Shane (Box 65)
  - Bernard Shane (Box 65, Folder 1)
- Moe Diamond (Box 66)
  - Moe Diamond, 1974 (Box 66, Folder 1)
    O.H. 1
- Moe Diamond (Box 67)
  - Moe Diamond, 1974 (Box 67, Folder 1)
- Josephine Stein (Box 68)
  - Josephine Stern, 1976 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    O.H. 14
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 69)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    O.H. 15
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 70)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975 (Box 70, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 71)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975 (Box 71, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 72)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975 (Box 72, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 73)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975 (Box 73, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 74)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975 (Box 74, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 75)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975 (Box 75, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 76)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975 (Box 76, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 77)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975 (Box 77, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 78)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975 (Box 78, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 79)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975 (Box 79, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 80)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975 (Box 80, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 81)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975 (Box 81, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 82)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975 (Box 82, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 83)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975 (Box 83, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 84)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975 (Box 84, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 85)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975 (Box 85, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 86)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975 (Box 86, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 87)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975 (Box 87, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 88)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975 (Box 88, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 89)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975 (Box 89, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 90)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975 (Box 90, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 91)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975 (Box 91, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 92)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975 (Box 92, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 93)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975 (Box 93, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 94)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975 (Box 94, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 95)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975 (Box 95, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 96)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975 (Box 96, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 97)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975 (Box 97, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 98)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975 (Box 98, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 99)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975 (Box 99, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 100)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975 (Box 100, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 101)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975 (Box 101, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 102)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975 (Box 102, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 103)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975 (Box 103, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 104)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975 (Box 104, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 105)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975 (Box 105, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 106)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975 (Box 106, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 107)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975 (Box 107, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 108)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975 (Box 108, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 109)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975 (Box 109, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 110)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975 (Box 110, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 111)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975 (Box 111, Folder 1)
- Murray Gross (Box 112)
  - Murray Gross, 1977 (Box 112, Folder 1)
    O.H. 16
- Murray Gross (Box 113)
  - Murray Gross, 1977 (Box 113, Folder 1)
- Murray Gross (Box 114)
  - Murray Gross, 1977 (Box 114, Folder 1)
- Murray Gross (Box 115)
  - Murray Gross, 1977 (Box 115, Folder 1)
- Murray Gross (Box 116)
  - Murray Gross, 1977 (Box 116, Folder 1)
- Murray Gross (Box 117)
  - Murray Gross, 1977 (Box 117, Folder 1)
- Murray Gross (Box 118)
  - Murray Gross, 1977 (Box 118, Folder 1)
- Murray Gross (Box 119)
  - Murray Gross, 1977 (Box 119, Folder 1)
- Murray Gross (Box 120)
  - Murray Gross, 1977 (Box 120, Folder 1)
- Murray Gross (Box 121)
  - Murray Gross, 1977 (Box 121, Folder 1)
- Murray Gross (Box 122)
  - Murray Gross, 1977 (Box 122, Folder 1)
- Murray Gross (Box 123)
  - Murray Gross, 1977 (Box 123, Folder 1)
- Murray Gross (Box 124)
  - Murray Gross, 1977 (Box 124, Folder 1)
- Enrico Parenti (Box 125)
  - Enrico Parenti, 1974 (Box 125, Folder 1)
    O.H. 17
- Enrico Parenti (Box 126)
  - Enrico Parenti, 1974 (Box 126, Folder 1)
- Enrico Parenti (Box 127)
  - Enrico Parenti, 1974 (Box 127, Folder 1)
- Bertha Mandel Laxner (Box 128)
  - Bertha Mandel Laxner, 1978 (Box 128, Folder 1)
    O.H. 18
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 129)
  - Abraham Plotkin (Box 129, Folder 1)
    O.H. 19
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 130)
  - Abraham Plotkin (Box 130, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 131)
  - Abraham Plotkin (Box 131, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 132)
  - Abraham Plotkin (Box 132, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 133)
  - Abraham Plotkin (Box 133, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 134)
  - Abraham Plotkin (Box 134, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 135)
  - Abraham Plotkin (Box 135, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 136)
  - Abraham Plotkin (Box 136, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 137)
  - Abraham Plotkin (Box 137, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 138)
  - Abraham Plotkin (Box 138, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 139)
  - Abraham Plotkin (Box 139, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 140)
  - Abraham Plotkin (Box 140, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 141)
  - Abraham Plotkin (Box 141, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 142)
  - Abraham Plotkin (Box 142, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 143)
  - Abraham Plotkin (Box 143, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 144)
  - Abraham Plotkin (Box 144, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 145)
  - Abraham Plotkin (Box 145, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 146)
  - Abraham Plotkin (Box 146, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 147)
  - Abraham Plotkin (Box 147, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 148)
  - Abraham Plotkin (Box 148, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 149)
  - Abraham Plotkin (Box 149, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 150)
  - Abraham Plotkin (Box 150, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 151)
  - Abraham Plotkin (Box 151, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 152)
  - Abraham Plotkin (Box 152, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 153)
  - Abraham Plotkin (Box 153, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 154)
  - Abraham Plotkin (Box 154, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 155)
  - Abraham Plotkin (Box 155, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 156)
  - Abraham Plotkin (Box 156, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 157)
  - Abraham Plotkin (Box 157, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 158)
  - Abraham Plotkin (Box 158, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 159)
  - Abraham Plotkin (Box 159, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 160)
  - Abraham Plotkin (Box 160, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 161)
  - Abraham Plotkin (Box 161, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 162)
  - Abraham Plotkin (Box 162, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 163)
  - Abraham Plotkin (Box 163, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 164)
  - Abraham Plotkin (Box 164, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 165)
  - Abraham Plotkin (Box 165, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 166)
  - Abraham Plotkin (Box 166, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 167)
  - Abraham Plotkin (Box 167, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 168)
  - Abraham Plotkin (Box 168, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 169)
  - Abraham Plotkin (Box 169, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 170)
  - Abraham Plotkin (Box 170, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 171)
  - Abraham Plotkin (Box 171, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 172)
  - Abraham Plotkin (Box 172, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 173)
  - Abraham Plotkin (Box 173, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 174)
  - Abraham Plotkin (Box 174, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 175)
  - Abraham Plotkin (Box 175, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 176)
  - Abraham Plotkin (Box 176, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 177)
  - Abraham Plotkin (Box 177, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 178)
  - Abraham Plotkin (Box 178, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 179)
  - Abraham Plotkin (Box 179, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 180)
  - Abraham Plotkin (Box 180, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 181)
  - Abraham Plotkin (Box 181, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 182)
  - Abraham Plotkin (Box 182, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 183)
  - Abraham Plotkin (Box 183, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 184)
  - Abraham Plotkin (Box 184, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 185)
  - Abraham Plotkin (Box 185, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 186)
  - Abraham Plotkin (Box 186, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 187)
  - Abraham Plotkin (Box 187, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 188)
  - Abraham Plotkin (Box 188, Folder 1)
- Frank Gatti (Box 189)
  - Frank Gatti, 1979 (Box 189, Folder 1)
    O.H. 20
- Frank Gatti (Box 190)
  - Frank Gatti, 1979 (Box 190, Folder 1)
- Frank Gatti (Box 191)
  - Frank Gatti, 1979 (Box 191, Folder 1)
- Frank Gatti (Box 192)
  - Frank Gatti, 1979 (Box 192, Folder 1)
- Frank Gatti (Box 193)
  - Frank Gatti, 1979 (Box 193, Folder 1)
- Frank Gatti (Box 194)
  - Frank Gatti, 1979 (Box 194, Folder 1)
- Frank Gatti (Box 195)
  - Frank Gatti, 1979 (Box 195, Folder 1)
- Frank Gatti (Box 196)
  - Frank Gatti, 1979 (Box 196, Folder 1)
- Frank Gatti (Box 197)
  - Frank Gatti, 1979 (Box 197, Folder 1)
- Shelley Appleton (Box 198)
  - Shelley Appleton, 1979 (Box 198, Folder 1)
    O.H. 21
- Samuel Weiss (Box 199)
  - Samuel Weiss, 1981 (Box 199, Folder 1)
    O.H. 22
- Lazare Teper (Box 200)
  - Lazare Teper, 1981-1984 (Box 200, Folder 1)
    O.H. 23
- Lazare Teper (Box 201)
  - Lazare Teper, 1981-1984 (Box 201, Folder 1)
- Lazare Teper (Box 202)
  - Lazare Teper, 1981-1984 (Box 202, Folder 1)
- Lazare Teper (Box 203)
  - Lazare Teper, 1981-1984 (Box 203, Folder 1)
- Lazare Teper (Box 204)
  - Lazare Teper, 1981-1984 (Box 204, Folder 1)
- Lazare Teper (Box 205)
  - Lazare Teper, 1981-1984 (Box 205, Folder 1)
- Lazare Teper (Box 206)
  - Lazare Teper, 1981-1984 (Box 206, Folder 1)
- Lazare Teper (Box 207)
  - Lazare Teper, 1981-1984 (Box 207, Folder 1)
- Lazare Teper (Box 208)
  - Lazare Teper, 1981-1984 (Box 208, Folder 1)
- Lazare Teper (Box 209)
  - Lazare Teper, 1981-1984 (Box 209, Folder 1)
- Lazare Teper (Box 210)
  - Lazare Teper, 1981-1984 (Box 210, Folder 1)
- Lazare Teper (Box 211)
  - Lazare Teper, 1981-1984 (Box 211, Folder 1)
- Lazare Teper (Box 212)
  - Lazare Teper, 1981-1984 (Box 212, Folder 1)
- Lazare Teper (Box 213)
  - Lazare Teper, 1981-1984 (Box 213, Folder 1)
- Lazare Teper (Box 214)
  - Lazare Teper, 1981-1984 (Box 214, Folder 1)
- Lazare Teper (Box 215)
  - Lazare Teper, 1981-1984 (Box 215, Folder 1)
- Lazare Teper (Box 216)
  - Lazare Teper, 1981-1984 (Box 216, Folder 1)
- Lazare Teper (Box 217)
  - Lazare Teper, 1981-1984 (Box 217, Folder 1)
- Lazare Teper (Box 218)
  - Lazare Teper, 1981-1984 (Box 218, Folder 1)
- Lazare Teper (Box 219)
  - Lazare Teper, 1981-1984 (Box 219, Folder 1)
- Lazare Teper (Box 220)
  - Lazare Teper, 1981-1984 (Box 220, Folder 1)
- Lazare Teper (Box 221)
  - Lazare Teper, 1981-1984 (Box 221, Folder 1)
- Lazare Teper (Box 222)
  - Lazare Teper, 1981-1984 (Box 222, Folder 1)
- Lazare Teper (Box 223)
  - Lazare Teper, 1981-1984 (Box 223, Folder 1)
- Lazare Teper (Box 224)
  - Lazare Teper, 1981-1984 (Box 224, Folder 1)
- Lazare Teper (Box 225)
  - Lazare Teper, 1981-1984 (Box 225, Folder 1)
- Lazare Teper (Box 226)
  - Lazare Teper, 1981-1984 (Box 226, Folder 1)
- Lazare Teper (Box 227)
  - Lazare Teper, 1981-1984 (Box 227, Folder 1)
- Lazare Teper (Box 228)
  - Lazare Teper, 1981-1984 (Box 228, Folder 1)
- Lazare Teper (Box 229)
  - Lazare Teper, 1981-1984 (Box 229, Folder 1)
- Israel Breslow (Box 230)
  - Israel Breslow, 1981-1984 (Box 230, Folder 1)
    O.H. 24
- Israel Breslow (Box 231)
  - Israel Breslow, 1981-1984 (Box 231, Folder 1)
- Israel Breslow (Box 232)
  - Israel Breslow, 1981-1982 (Box 232, Folder 1)
- Israel Breslow (Box 233)
  - Israel Breslow, 1981-1982 (Box 233, Folder 1)
- Israel Breslow (Box 234)
  - Israel Breslow, 1981-1982 (Box 234, Folder 1)
- Israel Breslow (Box 235)
  - Israel Breslow, 1981-1982 (Box 235, Folder 1)
- Israel Breslow (Box 236)
  - Israel Breslow, 1981-1982 (Box 236, Folder 1)
- Israel Breslow (Box 237)
  - Israel Breslow, 1981-1982 (Box 237, Folder 1)
- Israel Breslow (Box 238)
  - Israel Breslow, 1981-1982 (Box 238, Folder 1)
- Israel Breslow (Box 239)
  - Israel Breslow, 1981-1982 (Box 239, Folder 1)
- Israel Breslow (Box 240)
  - Israel Breslow, 1981-1982 (Box 240, Folder 1)
- Israel Breslow (Box 241)
  - Israel Breslow, 1981-1982 (Box 241, Folder 1)
- Israel Breslow (Box 242)
  - Israel Breslow, 1981-1982 (Box 242, Folder 1)
- Israel Breslow (Box 243)
  - Israel Breslow, 1981-1982 (Box 243, Folder 1)
- Israel Breslow (Box 244)
  - Israel Breslow, 1981-1982 (Box 244, Folder 1)
- Israel Breslow (Box 245)
  - Israel Breslow, 1981-1982 (Box 245, Folder 1)
- Israel Breslow (Box 246)
  - Israel Breslow, 1981-1982 (Box 246, Folder 1)
- Israel Breslow (Box 247)
  - Israel Breslow, 1981-1982 (Box 247, Folder 1)
- Israel Breslow (Box 248)
  - Israel Breslow, 1981-1982 (Box 248, Folder 1)
- Israel Breslow (Box 249)
  - Israel Breslow, 1981-1982 (Box 249, Folder 1)
- Israel Breslow (Box 250)
  - Israel Breslow, 1981-1982 (Box 250, Folder 1)
- Israel Breslow (Box 251)
  - Israel Breslow, 1981-1982 (Box 251, Folder 1)
- Israel Breslow (Box 252)
  - Israel Breslow, 1981-1982 (Box 252, Folder 1)
- Israel Breslow (Box 253)
  - Israel Breslow, 1981-1982 (Box 253, Folder 1)
- Israel Breslow (Box 254)
  - Israel Breslow, 1981-1982 (Box 254, Folder 1)
- Israel Breslow (Box 255)
  - Israel Breslow, 1981-1982 (Box 255, Folder 1)
- Israel Breslow (Box 256)
  - Israel Breslow, 1981-1982 (Box 256, Folder 1)
- Israel Breslow (Box 257)
  - Israel Breslow, 1981-1982 (Box 257, Folder 1)
- Israel Breslow (Box 258)
  - Israel Breslow, 1981-1982 (Box 258, Folder 1)
- Israel Breslow (Box 259)
  - Israel Breslow, 1981-1982 (Box 259, Folder 1)
- Israel Breslow (Box 260)
  - Israel Breslow, 1981-1982 (Box 260, Folder 1)
- Israel Breslow (Box 261)
  - Israel Breslow, 1981-1982 (Box 261, Folder 1)
- Israel Breslow (Box 262)
  - Israel Breslow, 1981-1982 (Box 262, Folder 1)
- Israel Breslow (Box 263)
  - Israel Breslow, 1981-1982 (Box 263, Folder 1)
- Moe Diamond (Box 264)
  - Moe Diamond, 1974 (Box 264, Folder 1)
- Moe Diamond (Box 265)
  - Moe Diamond, 1974 (Box 265, Folder 1)
- David Dubinsky (Box 266)
  - David Dubinsky, 1974 (Box 266, Folder 1)
- David Dubinsky (Box 267)
  - David Dubinsky, 1974 (Box 267, Folder 1)
- David Dubinsky (Box 268)
  - David Dubinsky, 1974 (Box 268, Folder 1)
- David Dubinsky (Box 269)
  - David Dubinsky, 1974 (Box 269, Folder 1)
- Pauline Newman (Box 270)
  - Pauline Newman, 1973 (Box 270, Folder 1)
    O.H. 4
- Pauline Newman (Box 271)
  - Pauline Newman, 1973 (Box 271, Folder 1)
- Emil Schlesinger (Box 272)
  - Emil Schlesinger, 1974 (Box 272, Folder 1)
- Emil Schlesinger (Box 273)
  - Emil Schlesinger, 1974 (Box 273, Folder 1)
- Emil Schlesinger (Box 274)
  - Emil Schlesinger, 1974 (Box 274, Folder 1)
- Emil Schlesinger (Box 275)
  - Emil Schlesinger, 1974 (Box 275, Folder 1)
- Emil Schlesinger (Box 276)
  - Emil Schlesinger, 1974 (Box 276, Folder 1)
- Emil Schlesinger (Box 277)
  - Emil Schlesinger, 1974 (Box 277, Folder 1)
- Emil Schlesinger (Box 278)
  - Emil Schlesinger, 1974 (Box 278, Folder 1)
- Emil Schlesinger (Box 279)